The veggie burger: this humble non-meat burger substitute is a staple of many a vegetarian meal.
素食汉堡：这种豪不起眼的非肉类汉堡替代品是许多素食餐的主食。
Though vegetarianism has a long history that reaches as far back as Egyptian times, and while many a vegetable-only stand-in patty is likely to have been used in the interim, the term veggie burger is commonly attributed to a Gregory Sams of London, who in 1982 created the 'Vegeburger'.
尽管素食主义的历史可以追溯到古埃及时期，而且在此期间可能已经出现了许多纯蔬菜的替代肉饼，但“素食汉堡”一词通常归功于伦敦的格雷戈里・萨姆斯（Gregory Sams），他在1982年创造了“Vegeburger”。
So what is a veggie burger?
那么什么是素食汉堡呢？
Well, a hamburger is a meat patty between two halves of a bun.
汉堡是两半（小圆）面包之间夹肉饼。
A veggie burger is similar, except the patty is a meat-free equivalent, commonly made from ingredients such as beans, tofu, nuts, grains and mushrooms.
素食汉堡类似，只不过肉饼是无肉的替代品，通常由豆类、豆腐、坚果、谷物和蘑菇等原料制成。
In many cases, the differences between the meat patty and vegetarian surrogate are clear, but Impossible Foods of Silicon Valley hope to put an end to that.
在许多情况下，肉饼和素食替代品之间的区别很明显，但硅谷的Impossible Foods公司希望终结这一点。
The Impossible burger is made of a plant-based iron-containing molecule that resembles blood.
Impossible汉堡由一种类似血液的植物性含铁分子制成。
It's called 'heme' and it's a key ingredient in their wheat, coconut and potato-based meat duplicate.
这种分子被称为“血红素”（heme），是以小麦、椰子和土豆为基础的肉类复制品的关键成分。
It apparently looks, smells and even bleeds like meat – but it's grown in a lab using biochemistry.
它看起来、闻起来甚至像肉一样“流血”——但它是在实验室中通过生物化学技术培育的。
This replicated burger is indistinguishable from meat 47% of the time in tests conducted among meat lovers, Impossible claims.
Impossible公司声称，在肉食爱好者中进行的测试显示，这种复制的汉堡有47%的比例无法区分出来。
There are many non-meat alternatives that are designed to closely imitate meat and many non-vegetarians might wonder why.
有许多非肉类替代品旨在密切模仿肉类，许多非素食者可能会想知道为什么。
Marketing is one good reason: faux-meat products appeal to meat-lover and vegetarian alike due to their alleged health benefits.
市场营销是一个很好的理由：人造的肉产品因其所谓的健康益处而吸引肉食爱好者和素食者。
If you can have the food you love at a lower health cost, why wouldn't you?
如果你能以更低的健康成本享用你喜爱的食物，为什么不呢？
Another reason is more ethical.
另一个原因更关乎伦理。
Many people stop eating meat for moral reasons rather than dietary ones.
许多人停止吃肉是出于道德原因而非饮食原因。
They may seek to reduce animal suffering by boycotting meat products or wish to reduce the meat industry's large environmental impact.
他们可能通过抵制肉类产品来试图减少动物的痛苦，或者希望减少肉类行业对环境的巨大影响。
Livestock production is responsible for 18% of total greenhouse gases, according to the Food and Agriculture Organisation (FAO).
根据联合国粮食及农业组织（FAO）的数据，畜牧业生产占温室气体总量的18%。
However, they may still miss the taste of meat.
然而，他们可能仍然怀念肉的味道。
Therefore pseudo-meat is a nice fill-in.
因此，“假”肉是一个很好的替代品。
Finally, "there are associated feelings and memories that go with certain foods," says Thomas Banks, BBC Learning English producer and 15-year vegetarian.
最后，BBC英语学习节目制作人、15年素食者托马斯・班克斯（Thomas Banks）说：“某些食物会带来相关的情感和回忆。
"I didn't grow up a vegetarian and sometimes I miss my family's cooking.
我小时候并不是素食主义者，有时我会怀念家人做的饭菜。
Replica meat allows me to have a good home-cooked meal that's just like mum used to make."
仿制肉让我能吃到一顿美味的家常菜，就像妈妈以前做的那样。”
Who can argue with that?
这谁能反驳呢？